airlockalpha.com 2014-11-29

# Privacy Policy | Airlock Alpha

We take privacy very seriously on the BlipNetwork sites, and want to make sure that you feel comfortable and safe while visiting any sites owned by Quantum Global Media Inc.

Because of that, we have chosen to spell out instances when identifying information may be collected based on your use of these Web sites, and how such information would be handled.

Quantum Global Media Inc. may collect Internet Protocol addresses from its content service provider as a means to maintain the site and correct issues which may arise, as well as for the general administration of its site. An no time does Quantum Global Media collect what would be described as personal identifiable information from those who have not provided it to us specifically.

Because the BlipNetwork sites contain links to other sites which are not owned and operated by Quantum Global Media Inc., we are not responsible for their privacy policies, and anyone using those sites should familiarize themselves with those policies.

From time to time, we may ask for you to provide personal identifiable information as a means to collect data for contests, research or other programs. All information provided will be on a voluntary basis, although failure to provide such information may disqualify continued involvement in those contests, research or other programs.

We use third party advertising companies to display advertising on the BlipNetwork sites which may contain cookies or be able to provide geographic-specific or term search specific advertising for your use. At no time does Quantum Global Media Inc. collect personal identifiable information. One of those third party vendors, Google, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.  
Google's use of the DoubleClick DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on your visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.  
You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting [the Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

BlipNetwork sites do not contain any pornographic elements, however, its text content is not censored, and thus does include adult language. The sites are not intended for those under 13, and no one under the age of 13 is allowed to submit personal information with any BlipNetwork or Quantum Global Media Inc. site. Quantum Global Media Inc. will never knowingly collect personal information from those under 13.

Further questions about Quantum Global Media Inc.'s privacy policy can be directed to Michael Hinman at mhinman@airlockalpha.com.
